Guide to the ACT UP New York records, 1969, 1982-1997 [bulk 1987-1995]
The New York Public Library. Manuscripts and Archives Division.
- Series XIII. Artifacts, circa 1987-1990, 1992, circa 1994, 1997, n.d; 558075; 9 boxes
  - Masks and signs, 558092
    - No choice of doctor? What's your problem?, circa 1994 Mar 14; 558098; This sign may have been worn at a demonstration protesting Mayor Giuliani's proposed elimination of New York City's Division of AIDS Services (DAS) on March 14, 1994.; Sign hung around the neck (Box 210)
    - No drug coverage? What's the big deal?, circa 1994 Mar 14; 558099; This sign may have been worn at a demonstration protesting Mayor Giuliani's proposed elimination of New York City's Division of AIDS Services (DAS) on March 14, 1994.; Sign hung around the neck (Box 210)
    - Our budget's been cut. We can't handle your complaint., circa 1994 Mar 14; 558100; This sign may have been worn at a demonstration protesting Mayor Giuliani's proposed elimination of New York City's Division of AIDS Services (DAS) on March 14, 1994.; Sign hung around the neck (Box 210)
    - Regulate the industry? Why??, circa 1994 Mar 14; 558101; This sign may have been worn at a demonstration protesting Mayor Giuliani's proposed elimination of New York City's Division of AIDS Services (DAS) on March 14, 1994.; Sign hung around the neck (Box 210)
    - Signs attached to a styrofoam handle, 558102; Flip sign (Box 213)
      - Question the statistic., 558103
      - Waffle. Verso: We need women in all phases., 558104
      - Lies. Verso: Not good enough., 558105
      - Duh., 558106
  - Paper cut-outs, 558107
    - Bandaid, 558108; Paper cut-out, painted beige (Box 212)
    - New York state, n.d.; 558109; Paper cut-out, colored red with marker (Box 212)
    - Scissors, n.d.; 558110; Paper cut-out, from photocopy (Box 212)
  - Stickers, 558111
    - Don't be silent. ACT UP for your life., n.d.; 558112; Stickers (Box 209)
    - The government has blood on its hands. One AIDS death every half hour., 1988; 558113; This graphic was created by Gran Fury.; Stickers (Box 209)
    - Silence = Death, n.d.; 558114; This graphic was created by the Silence = Death Project.; Stickers (Box 209)
    - Silencio = Muerte, n.d.; 558115; This graphic may have been created by the Silence = Death Project.; Stickers (Box 209)
    - Stop Helms. Miller Boycott., n.d.; 558116; Stickers (Box 209)
  - Miscellaneous, 558117
    - City AIDS Actions. Fight AIDS: Dump Rudy [Giuliani], n.d.; 558118; Condoms (Box 208)
    - Correspondence requesting merchandise order form, 558119 (Box 214)
    - Demand AIDS treatment access for all, 1997 Mar 24; 558120; This bottle may have been used at the "Crash the Market, 10th Anniversary Action" demonstration on Wall Street on Mar. 24, 1997.; Mock prescription pill bottle (Box 208)
    - Homecoming A.R.E.A. The American Run for the End of AIDS., circa 1987 Oct 31; 558121; Handheld flag (Box 212)
    - Oxygen mask, n.d.; 558122 (Box 215)
    - T Cell: 200 = AIDS, n.d.; 558123; Ping pong ball and sign (Box 208)
- Series XIV. Posters and placards, 1986, circa 1988-circa 1995, 1997, n.d; 558124; 13 oversize boxes, 4 oversize folders, 4 tubes, 1 oversize item
  Series XIV. Posters and placards is arranged in two subseries: XIV.A. Posters, 1986, circa 1988-circa 1995, n.d., and XIV.B. Placards, circa 1992-circa 1993, circa 1995, n.d. This series contains graphics used by ACT UP at demonstrations and events. Highly effective at using graphics to get across their point of view, ACT UP's posters and placards are colorful and dramatic. To understand the organization's varying graphic style dependent on member creativity and effort, the following series should also be viewed: Series XIII. Artifacts and Series XI. Ephemera, fliers, and handbills. The materials in this series have not been microfilmed; however, they are reproduced in the NYPL Digital Gallery and individual image ID numbers are provided: http://digitalgallery.nypl.org/nypldigital/dgkeysearchresult.cfm?parent_id=1060819&word=.
  - XIV.A. Posters, 1986, circa 1988-1995, 1997, n.d; 558125; 1 oversize box, 4 oversize folders, 4 tubes, 1 oversize item
    Subseries XIV.A. Posters is arranged alphabetically by title. Titles have been taken from the text on the posters.
    - ACT UP, 558126
      - ACT UP Reports on Sale Here, circa 1989 Jun; 558127; 1577291 (Box 217, Folder 1)
      - AIDS Is a Primary Issue. Demand a National Plan on AIDS., circa 1992; 558128; 1577292 (Box 217, Folder 1)
      - AIDS Is a Primary Issue. The Republicans Want Us Dead. The Democrats Don't Care., circa 1992 Feb 15; 558129; 1577293 (Box 217, Folder 1)
      - AIDS Treatment for All! ACT UP. Verso: Health Care Cuts Kill People with AIDS. ACT UP., n.d.; 558130; 1635828; Posters mounted on styrofoam (Map-case C-14)
      - AIDS: It's Big Business! (But Who's Making a Killing?), 1989; 558131; 1583384 (Box XX-14, Folder 1)
      - The All-Greed Journal, 1997 Mar 24; 558132; Created for the "Crash the Market, 10th Anniversary Action" on March 24, 1997. 1635829; Newsprint (Box XX-14, Folder 1)
      - American Flag [Our Government Continues to Ignore the Lives, Deaths and Suffering of People with HIV Infection... ], circa 1989 Jul 4; 558133; 1582124, 1584205 (Box 217, Folder 1)
      - Ask Carlo How He Feels about the AIDS Drug that's Costing Him $30,000 a Year, n.d.; 558134; 1577294 (Box 217, Folder 1)
      - Boycott Miller. Helm$ = Death., n.d.; 558135; 1583386 (Box XX-14, Folder 1)
      - Bush AIDS Flag, n.d.; 558136; 1583358 (Map-case C-14)
      - Capital Action. We Demand a Cure for the AIDS Crisis. Universal Heatlh Care., circa 1991 Oct 1; 558137; 1577317 (Box 217, Folder 10)
      - Crash the Market, 10th Anniversary Action, circa 1997 Mar; 558138; 1635830 (Box 217, Folder 2)
      - Cures Not Wars... March against Giuliani's Crackdown., n.d.; 558139; 1577296 (Box 217, Folder 2)
      - Deadlier than the Virus, n.d.; 558140; 1583388 (Box 217, Folder 2)
      - Deadlier than the Virus. Stephen C. Joseph, Commissioner of Health, NYC, circa 1985-1990; 558141; 1635826 (Map-case C-14)
      - Debate ACT UP? "I don't debate intellectual bomb throwers and terrorists," Herbert Kleber, 558142; Final poster titled "Meet with ACT UP? 'I don't debate intellectual bomb throwers and terrorists,' Herbert Kleber." 1577297; Draft (Box 217, Folder 6)
      - Declare War. Target an Administration that Kills Us with Neglect. Storm the NIH., circa 1990 May 21; 558143; 1577298, 1581561 (Box 217, Folder 3)
      - Demand a Cure for the AIDS Crisis., circa 1991 May 13; 558144; 1577299 (Box 217, Folder 3)
      - Demand McClintock. The Plan to Find a Cure., 558145; 1577342 (Box 223)
      - Demonstrate. NYCHA's Gonna Getcha Evicted for Being Gay., n.d.; 558146; 1577300 (Box 217, Folder 3)
      - Do Not Be Fooled by David Souter, circa 1990 Sep; 558147; 1577302, 1581859 (Box 217, Folder 4)
      - Don't Gag Me, Sununu!, n.d.; 558148; 1577301 (Box 217, Folder 4)
      - Enjoy AZT, circa 1991 May; 558149; 1583380; Newsprint (Box 217, Folder 4)
      - Fashion for Action, circa 1991 Mar; 558150; 1577303 (Box 217, Folder 4)
      - Free Health Care. Stop Forced HIV Testing of Health Care Workers., n.d.; 558151; 1577304 (Box 217, Folder 5)
      - Honor a Tradition... ACT UP for Medical Marijuana!, n.d.; 558152; 1577305 (Box 217, Folder 5)
      - If You Fuck without a Condom You Risk HIV Infection and Can Get AIDS., 558153; 1577306 (Box XX-14, Folder 1)
      - If You Fuck without a Condom You Risk HIV Infection and Can Get AIDS., 558154 (Map-case C-14)
      - Living with AIDS. Dying from Our Mayor. [Giuliani], circa 1995 Jun 28; 558155; 1577307 (Box 217, Folder 5)
      - Mandatory HIV Testing Is Here! INS., circa 1990 Jun; 558156; 1583376 (Box 217, Folder 6)
      - March on the Candidates... AIDS Is a Primary Issue, circa 1992; 558157; 1577308 (Box 217, Folder 6)
      - Meet with ACT UP? "I don't debate intellectual bomb-throwers and terrorists," Herbert Kleber, 558158; 1577309 (Box 217, Folder 6)
      - Mientras la nacion se "mueve" a la derecha... a cuantas personas con SIDA pisotearan? [Gingrich], 1995 Jan 8; 558159; 1577310 (Box 217, Folder 6)
      - Official Gannett Outdoor Creative Challenge Work-sheet. People Being Cured of AIDS: 000,000,000,000., n.d.; 558160; 1583392 (Box 217, Folder 7)
      - One AIDS Death Every 12 Minutes, circa 1990 May; 558161; 1577311 (Box 217, Folder 7)
      - 150,000 Dead from AIDS. Stop this Monster! [Bush], n.d.; 558162; 1577312 (Box XX-14, Folder 2)
      - Pediatrics AIDS Caucus, n.d.; 558163; This item is missing as of March 14, 2008. 1577324
      - Stop Gay-Bashing at the Board of Ed!, n.d.; 558164; 1577315 (Box 217, Folder 7)
      - Stop the Church, 558165
        - Asesino de Masas, 1994; 558166; 1582293; Photocopy (Box 217, Folder 8)
        - Catholics, Condoms, and AIDS [New York Times headline], circa 1989 Dec 10; 558167; 1582292 (Box 217, Folder 8)
        - The extent of AIDS among teenagers is going to be the next crisis... " Cardinal O'Connor Won't Teach Safe Sex, circa 1989 Dec 10; 558168; 1577314 (Box 217, Folder 8)
        - Misogino, 1994; 558169; 1582294; Photocopy (Box 217, Folder 8)
      - Target City Hall, 558170
        - Reason #2 to ACT UP on March 28th... 5,000 People with AIDS Deserve a Better Place to Live than the Sidewalk You're Standing On, circa 1989 Mar 28; 558171; 1577313 (Box 217, Folder 9)
        - Reason #5 to ACT UP on March 28th... Since the City Cut AIDS Education, More Kids Get to Leave School Early, circa 1989 Mar 28; 558172; 1581860 (Box 217, Folder 9)
      - Target Rudy. Fight AIDS., 1994 Mar 22; 558173; 1577316, 1582295 [Spanish] (Box 217, Folder 9)
      - 10,000 New York City AIDS Deaths. How'm I doin'? [Koch], n.d.; 558174; 1582125, 1584206 (Box 217, Folder 10)
      - 13 Years of Failed Research. Demand the AIDS Cure Project, 558175; 1577376, 1577422; Black/white, 22.5" x 17.5" (Box 227)
      - Thomas A. Coughlin, III. The ACT UP Golden Shaft Award, n.d.; 558176; 1577295; Draft (Box 217, Folder 2)
      - Thomas A. Coughlin, III. The ACT UP Golden Shaft Award., n.d.; 558177; 1577321 (Item 2)
      - Welcome to NY. Stonewall 25., 1994 Jun; 558178; 1583377, 1583395, 1583396; Flier on newsprint (Box 217, Folder 11)
      - What Does Koch Plan to Do about AIDS? Invest in Marble and Granite., circa 1989 Mar 28; 558179; 1635827 (Map-case C-14)
      - What New York Promised in the Fight against AIDS..., n.d.; 558180; 1685831 (Box 217, Folder 10)
      - Women Don't Get AIDS. They Just Die from It., 558181; 1577318, 1581861 [Spanish] (Box 217, Folder 11)
      - You Can't Wear a Ribbon if You're Dead., n.d.; 558182; 1577319 (Box 217, Folder 11)
    - Other organizations, 558183
      - AIDS Requiem, circa 1990 Jan 6; 558184; Poster for Ed Baynard's show at the Marcuse Pfiefer Gallery, Jan 6-Feb 8, 1990. 1583357 (Box XX-14, Folder 1)
      - Apts. Lie Empty While People Die in the Streets, n.d.; 558185; 1583390 (Box 217, Folder 12)
      - Cardiac Arrest, 558186
        - Christian Lifestyle -- A Sin!!!, n.d.; 558187; 1583359 (Box 217, Folder 13)
        - Holocaust Candidates, 558188; 1583379 (Box 217, Folder 13)
        - Moderate Republicans [7 Ku Klux Klan hoods with names], n.d.; 558189; 1583365; Draft (Box 217, Folder 13)
        - Republican Roots: GOP/KKK, n.d.; 558190; 1583387 (Box 217, Folder 13)
        - Republican Roots: GOP/KKK, n.d.; 558191; 1583366; Draft (Box 217, Folder 13)
      - DCTV Lesbian and Gay Video Festival, circa 1992 Nov 10-15; 558192; 1583382, 1583890 (Box 217, Folder 12)
      - Gran Fury, 558193
        - AIDS Behind Bars, 1988; 558194; 1583391 (Box 217, Folder 12)
        - The Government Has Blood on Its Hands. One AIDS Death Every Half Hour., 1988; 558195; 1577320 (Item 1)
        - Kissing Doesn't Kill, 1989; 558196 (Map-case C-14)
        - Read My Lips (Boys), 1988; 558197; This image was created by Gran Fury as part of the National Spring AIDS Action '88 campaign. The verso of this poster contains an article titled, "Why We Kiss." 1583375, 1583394 (Box 217, Folder 12)
      - Haring, Keith. Silence = Death, 1989; 558198; 1577323 (Item 4)
      - Manifestation contre L'intervention Nord-Americaine en Haiti, n.d.; 558199; 1583383 (Box 217, Folder 12)
      - One AIDS Death Every Thirty Minutes, n.d.; 558200; 1583385 (Box XX-14, Folder 1)
      - Safe Sex Is Hot Sex. Use a Condom Every Time., 1991; 558201; This poster carries the Red, Hot, and Blue logo. 1583389 (Map-case C-14)
      - Semana Cultural Gay, circa 1989 Jun 14-23; 558202; 1583355 (Box XX-14, Folder 3)
      - Semana Cultural Gay, circa 1991 Jun 13-23, 20-28; 558203; 1583356 (Box XX-14, Folder 3)
      - Silence = Death Project. Silence = Death, 1986; 558204; Poster is torn. (Item 3)
      - Silence = Death Project. Silence = Death, 1986; 558205; 1577322 (Map-case C-14)
      - What about AIDS?, circa 1992 [?; 558206; 1583378, 1583397 (Box XX-14, Folder 2)
      - Women Get AIDS Too, n.d.; 558207; 1583381 (Box XX-14, Folder 2)
  - XIV.B. Placards, circa 1992-circa 1993, circa 1995, n.d; 558208; 12 oversize boxes
    Subseries XIV.B. Placards is arranged alphabetically by title. Titles were created from the text on the placards. While some of the placards are somber in tone, others are colorful and amusing. For example, in the Wizard of OZ series elected officials are depicted as the cowardly lion (President Clinton), the scarecrow (New York Gov. George Pataki), the tin man (New York City Mayor Rudolph Giuliani), and the wicked witch (Speaker of the House Newt Gingrich). Opposite in tone is the placard that reads: "The only way research is done on women." On this stark, black and white placard there is a picture of a scientist examining a human skull, with a skeleton hanging from a hook in the background. The organization advocated greater research on women and AIDS.
    - ACT UP. Clean Needles Save Lives. Needle Exchange Now! Verso: ACT UP. Una Aguja Limpia Salva Tidas. Intercambio de Agujas Ya!, n.d.; 558209; 1577325, 1577385; Black/white, 10" x 40" (Box 232)
    - The Board Moralizes -- Students Get AIDS. Verso: Students Are Dying for a Real AIDS Curriculum. YELL: Youth Education Life Line, n.d.; 558210; 1577327, 1577391; Black/white (Box 229)
    - Broken Promise 3: "Support Condom Availability in Schools" [Clinton]. Verso: [Same message in Spanish], 558211; 1577329, 1577392; Black/white, 40" x 30" (Box 232)
    - Buchanan AIDS Disaster. Campaign '92. Verso: Tsongas. Where's Your AIDS Plan?, circa 1992; 558212; 1577330, 1577393; Black/white, 30" x 20" (Box 222)
    - Bush AIDS Flag, n.d.; 558213; 1577332, 1577395; Color, 24" x 36" (Box 230)
    - Bush = Death. Elect to Live. Verso: Fight Republican Bigotry, circa 1992; 558214; 1577331, 1577394; Black/white, 30" x 20" (Box 222)
    - City Hall. AIDS. Rudy [Giuliani] to New Yorkers with AIDS: Drop Dead, n.d.; 558215; 1577333, 1577396; Black/white, 27" x 20" (Box 222)
    - Clinton to People with AIDS: Go Die in the Street. Verso: RIP. Killed by Clinton's AIDS Housing Cuts, n.d.; 558216; 1577334, 1577397; Color, 28" x 17" (Box 222)
    - Condoms or Casket. Verso: [Front page of New York Newsday with School Chancellor Joseph Fernandez and headline, "New Yorkers Favor School Condom Plan."] AIDS Education Is Common Sense., 558217; 1577335, 1577398; Color, 30" x 20" (Box 222)
    - El Coqui USA Condones. Verso: El Coqui Limpia sus Aparatos., 558218; 1577344, 1577404; Color, 20" x 30" (Box 223)
    - Criminales de SIDA [Cardinal O'Connor], n.d.; 558219; 1577336, 1577399; Color, 30" x 20" (Box 222)
    - Dead from Lack of Dignity and Respect. Verso: Living with AIDS. Dying from Our Mayor! [Giuliani], circa 1995 Jun; 558220; 1577340, 1577402; Black/white, 20" x 30" (Box 223)
    - Dead Women Can't Vote. Cure AIDS. Verso: ACT UP. Fight Back. Fight AIDS., n.d.; 558221; 1577341, 1577403; Black/white, yellow, 20" x 30" (Box 223)
    - Disaster Relief. AIDS Now., n.d.; 558222; 1577343; Color, 29.5" x 30" (Box 231)
    - El E.L.A. Me Mata [Puerto Rican flag], n.d.; 558223; 1577345; Color, 20" x 30" (Box 223)
    - FDA: Unsafe at Any Dosage. Verso: 100,000,000 Women in the US -- How Many Drugs Analyzed for Gender Effects?, 558224; 1577346, 1577405; Black/white, 30" x 20" (Box 224)
    - Fight AIDS. Verso: ACT UP, n.d.; 558225; 1577347, 1577406; Color, 19" x 15" (Box 220)
    - Fight AIDS. Demand an AIDS Cure Now! Verso: We Will Not Rest in Peace. ACT UP., 558226; 1577348, 1582127; Color, 30" x 20" (Box 224)
    - Fight AIDS. Ninfa Segarra: Anti-AIDS Deputy Mayor. Verso: We Will Not Rest in Peace. ACT UP., n.d.; 558227; 1577349, 1577407; Color, 30" x 20" (Box 224)
    - For People with AIDS a Cure Is Lightyears Away, n.d.; 558228; 1577350, 1577408; Black/white, color decal, 30" x 20" (Box 224)
    - Free Health Care. Stop Forced HIV Testing of Health Care Workers. Verso: No Witchhunt! No Forced Testing! No Way!, n.d.; 558229; 1577352, 1577410; Color, 24" x 18" (Box 220)
    - Free the Safe Sex Six., n.d.; 558230; 1577351, 1577409; Black/white, 20" x 30" (Box 224)
    - GOB. Hernandez Colon: AIDS Criminal, 558231; 1577339, 1577401; Black/white, red, 36" x 20" (Box 223)
    - Gov. Cuomo: We Need a Reprieve. Verso: [New York Post headline] Blue Cross Rate Hikes a "Death Warrant." The Buck Stops Here, circa 1993 Jan 2; 558232; 1577337, 1577400; Color, 24" x 18" (Box 222)
    - Health Care Cuts Kill, n.d.; 558233; 1577354; Color, 31" x 24" (Box 229)
    - Hemophilia and AIDS: The Preventable Plague. Verso: No More Cover Up! Hemophiliacs Deserve the Truth., 558234; 1577355, 1582290; Sandwich board, color (Box 220)
    - How Do You Spell: "Coalition for the Northern Dipensary"? NIMBY ("Not In My Back Yard")/You Know They Wouldn't Oppose AIDS Housing Here if It Was for White Boys Only. Verso: HIV is... crime.. .shut do..., 558235; 1577356, 1582291; Two fliers are posted on a board to make this placard; black/white, 14" x 22". (Box 220)
    - How Many of Us Will Be Alive for Stonewall 35? Verso: AIDS: Where Is Your Rage? ACT UP., n.d.; 558236; 1577357, 1577411; Black/white, red (Box 225)
    - If You Fuck without a Condom You Risk HIV Infection and Can Get AIDS, 558237; 1577362, 1582288; Color, 23.5" x 20" (Box 226)
    - In New York People with AIDS Have All the Money in the World. On Paper. Release the Funds! Verso: Wanted for Murder [Cuomo], 558238; 1577363, 1582289; Black/white, red, 30" x 20" (Box 226)
    - Killed by Koch, n.d.; 558239; 1577364; Color, 26" x 16" (Box 226)
    - Lesbian Furies, 558240; The Lesbian Furies created these placards.
      - HIV/AIDS Services for Women in Prison. Justice Now!!! Verso: ACT UP, n.d.; 558241; 1577353, 1582128; Color, 30" x 20" (Box 224)
      - Women Demand Access to Treatments, 558242; 1577383; Color, 30" x 20" (Box 228)
      - Women Positive. Drug Treatment Now!, n.d.; 558243; 1597274; Color (Box 228)
      - Women's Health Care. Up against the Wall., n.d.; 558244; 1577384; Color, (Box 228)
    - Let Me Demonstrate [Jesus Christ hammering a stake into Cardinal O'Connor's neck]. Veso: Let Me Demonstrate [Jesus Christ holding a condom], 558245; 1577365, 1582123; Color, 30" x 20" (Box 226)
    - Mr. Cuomo, Your AIDS Housing Plan Makes Us Sick, n.d.; 558246; 1577338; Color, 21" x 36.5" (Box 230)
    - Newt's Contract Kills People with AIDS. Verso: Deadlier than the Virus, n.d.; 558247; 1577367, 1577415; Black/white, 20" x 30" (Box 226)
    - No More Invisible Women. We're Dying for Data. Verso: Fair Pricing Now, n.d.; 558248; 1577368, 1577416; Black/white, 21" x 15" (Box 220)
    - Olga Mendez: Politica Criminal. Verso: Jose Serrano: Politico Criminal, 558249; 1577366, 1577414; Black/white, red, 30" x 20" (Box 226)
    - The Only Way Research Is Done on Women, n.d.; 558250; 1577372; Black/white, 30" x 20" (Box 226)
    - Open the Borders! Verso: Lift the HIV Ban. Free the Haitian Hunger Strikers., n.d.; 558251; 1577369, 1577417; Black/white and color, 20" x 32" (Box 229)
    - Provide AIDS Care in Prisons, n.d.; 558252; 1577370; Color, 30" x 29.5" (Box 231)
    - The Real Answer to New York's Health Care Crisis. Your NY Health Card. Verso: Cuomo's Solution for Health Care in New York: Band-Aids!!!, 558253; 1577371, 1577418; Color, 30" x 20" (Box 226)
    - Sick People Need Health Insurance. Verso: Gov. Pataki: We Can't Afford 45% More. ACT UP., n.d.; 558254; 1577373, 1577419; Black/white, 30" x 20", condom attached (Box 227)
    - Silencio = Muerte. Verso: 30 Gays Arrested Each Night in Buenos Aires. Shame!, n.d.; 558255; 1577374, 1577420; Color, 30" x 20" [?] (Box 227)
    - Stop the Pope. John Paul Is a Drag. Verso: Stop Homophobia. Gay Marriage Is a Right., n.d.; 558256; 1577375, 1577421; Black/white, 30" x 20" (Box 227)
    - 13 Years of Broken Promises. Verso: Demand the AIDS Cure Project., 558257; 1577377, 1577423; Black/white, 24" x 18" (Box 227)
    - This Is Harm. Verso: Needle Exchange Is Harm Reduction., n.d.; 558258; 1577378, 1577424; Black/white (Box 227)
    - Undercounting AIDS Cases Kills. Verso: The CDC Is a Dead End [Yellow diamond warning sign], 558259; 1577379, 1577425; Color, 20" x 20" (Box 227)
    - Veterans Park rally, New Hampshire], n.d.; 558260; 1577326; Multiple fliers, black/white, 20" x 30" (Box 222)
    - Virginity or Bust [Virgin Mary and Cardinal O'Connor], 558261; 1577380; Black/white, red, 28" x 22" (Box 228)
    - We're Fired Up, n.d.; 558262; 1577381; Color, 18" x 24" (Box 228)
    - What about AIDS? Rudy ACT UP Is Watching [Giuliani], n.d.; 558263; 1577382, 1597273; Black/white, red, 20" x 30" (Box 228)
    - Wizard of OZ, 558264
      - I'd Fight AIDS if I Only Had a Brain. Verso: Pataki: Medicaid Cuts Kill, n.d.; 558265; 1577358, 1583892; Color, 20" x 30" (Box 225)
      - I'd Fight AIDS if I Only Had the Courage. Verso: Bill: Support AIDS Cure Project [Clinton], n.d.; 558266; 1577359, 1577412; Color, 20" x 30" (Box 225)
      - I'd Fight AIDS if I Only Had the Heart. Verso: Rudy: Teach Safe Sex in Schools [Giuliani], n.d.; 558267; 1577360, 1577413; Color, 20" x 30" (Box 225)
      - I'll Get You My Pretty & Your T-Cells Too! Verso: Fight Back. Fight AIDS. Fight Newt [Gingrich]., n.d.; 558268; 1577361, 1583891; Color, 20" x 30" (Box 225)
- Series XV. Addenda, 1985-1997, n.d.; 558269; 10 boxes
  Series XV. Addenda contains additional material not listed in the original finding aid. It consists of administrative files, chapter information, conference materials, correspondence, demonstration ephemera, financial records, medical glossaries and fact sheets, periodicals, press clippings, press releases, and miscellany. The "Miscellaneous" folders include agendas, charts and notes, contact and phone lists, correspondence, drafts of letters and reports, fact sheets, financial records, handouts, journal articles, meeting announcements and fliers, merchandise order forms, notes, press clippings, press releases, and reports. This series has not been microfilmed.
  - ACT UP Chronology/Capsule History, circa 1988 Oct, circa 1991 Feb, circa 1994 May; 558270 (Box 233, Folder 1)
  - ACT UP Network, 558271; The ACT UP Network was a listing of national and international chapters' contact information and updates.
    - 1990 Sep, 1993 May, 1994 May, 1995 Mar-Jun, 1996 Jul, 1997, n.d, 558272 (Box 233, Folder 2)
    - Red Hot funds, 1991 Dec-circa 1993 Feb, 1995 Jul, 1996 Apr, Aug, n.d; 558273; Correspondence, financial records, press clippings (Box 233, Folder 3)
  - ACT UP Paris, 1989 May-1991, circa 1996 Apr. n.d; 558274; This folder contains material documenting the ACT UP chapter in Paris, France. (Box 233, Folder 4)
  - Administrative materials, circa 1993 Mar, 1995 Jun, 1996 Jun-Jul, n.d; 558275 (Box 233, Folder 5)
  - AIDS medical glossaries and miscellaneous medical/treatment materials, 1988-1989, 1995-1997, n.d; 558276 (Box 233, Folder 6)
  - Conferences, 558277
    - [Conference and meeting?] notes, 1993 Jan, n.d; 558278 (Box 233, Folder 7)